We can also turn deep think on or search on. So let's say that deep seek.
I want to gather information about an educational brand called The Take-Off College.
Could you please introduce it to me? And I turned the search on and I asked my command, so I sent my message.
And I wait a little bit.
To find an educational brand, especially by that name,
the search results revealed several similarity named educational programs with The Take-Off Institute.
Yes, I understand. So let's ask it, including the domain over here, right?
Let me say that. But what I'm searching for is called The Take-Off College.
The website is also TheTakeOffCollege.com as I know. And I saw some Udemy courses of them.
So search for me, please, right? And I asked my command to see where we end up.
The Take-Off College official website The Take-Off College Udemy courses, right?
And as you see, yes, an introduction to The Take-Off College based on Udemy instructor profile is an as you can independent international educational platform.
Philosophy, course style, and as you see course titles, right? So it goes and searches for us, as you see.
and we also have deep think I don't want to use that for now.